Finding Aid for the Alumni Relations Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Deceased Alumni
  - Cunningham, Wentworth P. (Box 2637, Folder 25)
  - Cunningham, William Alex (Box 2637, Folder 26)
  - Cunningham, William Moody (Box 2637, Folder 27)
  - Cunningham, Zachary Taylor (Box 2637, Folder 28)
  - Cupp, Vernon C. (Box 2637, Folder 29)
  - Cureton, Hugh E. (Box 2637, Folder 30)
  - Curham, Wilson Richard (Box 2637, Folder 31)
  - Curley, John Edward (Box 2637, Folder 32)
  - Curlin, Charles Wilson (Box 2637, Folder 33)
  - Curlin, Zachary H. (Box 2637, Folder 34)
  - Curran, Vincent A. (Box 2637, Folder 35)
  - Currey, Brownlee Owen (Folder 1 of 3) (Board of Trust Member) (Box 2637, Folder 36)
  - Currey, Brownlee Owen (Folder 2 of 3) (Board of Trust Member) (Box 2637, Folder 37)
  - Currey, Brownlee Owen (Folder 3 of 3) (Board of Trust Member) (Box 2637, Folder 38)
  - Currey, Louis Robert (Box 2637, Folder 39)
  - Currie, George Waddel (Box 2637, Folder 40)
  - Curry, Irby Rice (Box 2637, Folder 41)
  - Curry, J. R. (Box 2637, Folder 42)
  - Curry, James Thomas (Box 2637, Folder 43)
  - Curry, Joseph Lester (Box 2637, Folder 44)
  - Curry, Robert William (Box 2637, Folder 45)
  - Curry, Walter Clyde (Box 2637, Folder 46)
  - Curtis, Albert B. (Box 2637, Folder 47)
  - Curtis, Anita Bertran (Box 2637, Folder 48)
  - Curtis, George M. (Box 2637, Folder 49)
  - Curtis, Lynn Ferguson (Box 2637, Folder 50)
  - Curtis, Water Makepeace (Box 2637, Folder 51)
  - Curtis, William Marvette (Box 2637, Folder 52)
  - Curtiss, Betty Raymond (Box 2637, Folder 53)
  - Curtiss, Lyle Raymond (Box 2637, Folder 54)
  - Cushing, Daniel (Box 2637, Folder 55)
  - Cushman, Hampton Pharr (Box 2637, Folder 56)
  - Cutliff, Jerry Griffin (Box 2637, Folder 57)
  - Dabbs, John Wilson Thomas (Box 2637, Folder 58)
  - Dabney, Albert S. (Box 2637, Folder 59)
  - Dade, Randolph (Box 2637, Folder 60)
  - Dade, Robert Beverly (Box 2637, Folder 61)
  - Dahlinger, Charles E. and Anna Rose Siegrist (Wife) (Box 2637, Folder 62)
  - Dailey, Glenna May Wilkerson (Mrs. Thomas Dailey) (Box 2637, Folder 63)
  - Dailey, Thomas William and Glenna May Wilkerson (Wife) (Box 2637, Folder 64)
  - Daily, Henry Jackson (Box 2637, Folder 65)
  - Dake, Richard Wiggin (Box 2637, Folder 66)
  - Dake, Walter M. (Box 2637, Folder 67)
  - Dale, James Atchison (Box 2637, Folder 68)
  - Dale, Norman (Box 2637, Folder 69)
  - Dallas, Hugh Douglas (Box 2637, Folder 70)
  - Dalton, Erby Neal (Box 2637, Folder 71)
  - Dalton, J. S. (Box 2637, Folder 72)
  - Dameron, George Walton (Box 2637, Folder 73)
  - Damon, Henry Gordon (Box 2637, Folder 74)
  - Damrel, Elmore Green (Box 2637, Folder 75)
  - Dance, Edward Maze (Box 2637, Folder 76)
  - Dancy, Alexander Brown (Box 2637, Folder 77)
  - Daniel, Alonzo Wells (Box 2637, Folder 78)
  - Daniel, Charles Denson (Box 2637, Folder 79)
  - Daniel, Cliffe Atchison (Box 2637, Folder 80)
  - Daniel, David Wistar (Box 2637, Folder 81)
  - Daniel, Freeman Bozeman (Box 2637, Folder 82)
  - Daniel, James Harrison (Box 2637, Folder 83)
  - Daniel, James Walter Wright (Box 2637, Folder 84)
  - Daniel, Jerome W. (Box 2637, Folder 85)
  - Daniel, John Bernard (Box 2637, Folder 86)
  - Daniel, Ray Knight (Box 2637, Folder 87)
  - Daniel, Rollin Augustus (Box 2637, Folder 88)
  - Daniel, Rollin Augustus (Junior), Photo (Box 2637, Folder 89)
  - Daniel, Selman Adron (Box 2637, Folder 90)
  - Daniel, William Harris (Box 2637, Folder 91)
  - Daniel, William M. (Box 2637, Folder 92)
  - Daniel, William Nicks (Box 2637, Folder 93)
  - Daniel, William R. (Box 2637, Folder 94)
  - Daniel, William Thomas (Box 2637, Folder 95)
  - Daniels, James Addison (Box 2637, Folder 96)
  - Dankins, Virginia Nunez (Mrs. Edsel Dankins or Mrs. A. Domas) (Box 2637, Folder 97)
  - Danley, James Walter (Box 2637, Folder 98)
  - Danley, Noah (Box 2637, Folder 99)
  - Dann, Lester Winfield (Box 2637, Folder 100)
  - Dantzler, G. B. (Box 2637, Folder 101)
  - Dantzler, John Lewis (Board of Trust Member) (Box 2637, Folder 102)
  - Dantzler, Lehre Livingston (Box 2637, Folder 103)
  - Darden, Gordon Wallace (Box 2637, Folder 104)
  - Darden, Madge Rebecca (Box 2637, Folder 105)
  - Darden, Robert A. (Box 2637, Folder 106)
  - Dargan, Marion (Box 2637, Folder 107)
  - Dargan, Mary Louise Hodge (Mrs. Perrin Dargan) (Box 2637, Folder 108)
  - Darnall, James Franklin (Box 2637, Folder 109)
  - Darnall, Thomas Mauze (Box 2637, Folder 110)
  - Darrah, Charles Alexander (Box 2637, Folder 111)
  - Darwin, Charles Barnes (Box 2637, Folder 112)
  - Darwin, William Cyrus (Box 2637, Folder 113)
  - Dashiell, James Walker (Box 2637, Folder 114)
  - Daspit, John Warren (Box 2637, Folder 115)
  - Daugherty, Herbert Daniel (Box 2637, Folder 116)
  - Davenport, Charles Pierce (Box 2637, Folder 117)
  - Davenport, Francis Garvin (Box 2637, Folder 118)
  - Davenport, Milton (Box 2637, Folder 119)
  - Daves, James Herman (Box 2637, Folder 120)
  - David, Roscoe Samuel (Box 2637, Folder 121)
  - Davidson, Albert Alonzo (Box 2637, Folder 122)
  - Davidson, Carlie W. (Box 2637, Folder 123)
  - Davidson, Chester Logan (Box 2637, Folder 124)
  - Davidson, George Washington (Box 2637, Folder 125)
  - Davidson, Govan Caldwell (Box 2637, Folder 126)
  - Davidson, Harold Hall (Box 2637, Folder 127)
  - Davidson, James Stanley (Box 2637, Folder 128)
  - Davidson, Joseph Samuel (Box 2637, Folder 129)
  - Davidson, Murat H. and Mrs. Davidson (Box 2637, Folder 130)
  - Davidson, Robert Mitchell (Box 2637, Folder 131)
  - Davidson, Thomas Heber (Box 2637, Folder 132)
  - Davidson, William Wallace (Box 2637, Folder 133)
  - Davie, Mrs. Rorth W. (Box 2637, Folder 134)
  - Davies, Elmer D. (Box 2637, Folder 135)
  - Davin, Charles C. (Box 2637, Folder 136)
  - Davis, Alvis J. (Box 2637, Folder 137)
  - Davis, Andrew Lawson, Photo (Box 2637, Folder 138)
  - Davis, Benjamin T. (Box 2637, Folder 139)
  - Davis, Brucile Labelle Phillips (Mrs. Carl A. Davis) (Box 2637, Folder 140)
  - Davis, Cato Aristides (Box 2637, Folder 141)
  - Davis, Charles Harold (Box 2637, Folder 142)
  - Davis, Charles Paralee (Box 2637, Folder 143)
  - Davis, Charles T. (Box 2637, Folder 144)
  - Davis, Charles Thomas (Box 2637, Folder 145)
  - Davis, Charles W. (Box 2637, Folder 146)
  - Davis, Clement B. (Box 2637, Folder 147)
  - Davis, David Richard (Box 2637, Folder 148)
  - Davis, David Taylor (Box 2637, Folder 149)
  - Davis, Douglas Powell (Box 2637, Folder 150)
  - Davis, Duncan Eugene (Box 2637, Folder 151)
  - Davis, Edward Benjamin (Box 2637, Folder 152)
  - Davis, Ewin Lamar, United States Congressman (Box 2637, Folder 153)
  - Davis, Grace Keisler (Box 2637, Folder 154)
  - Davis, Hal Muncaster (Box 2637, Folder 155)
  - Davis, Hampton Tompkins and Bonnie Binning (Wife) (Box 2637, Folder 156)
  - Davis, Henry Ashburn (Box 2637, Folder 157)
  - Davis, Henry Earle and Lucille Johnson (Wife) (Box 2637, Folder 158)
  - Davis, James Murry (Box 2638, Folder 1)
  - Davis, James Orren (Box 2638, Folder 2)
  - Davis, James S. (Box 2638, Folder 3)
  - Davis, John Kemp (Box 2638, Folder 4)
  - Davis, John Lewis (Box 2638, Folder 5)
  - Davis, John Llewellyn (Box 2638, Folder 6)
  - Davis, John Love (Box 2638, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Joseph Ludwell (Box 2638, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Kenneth Forrest (Box 2638, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Lindsey M. (Box 2638, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Louis Andrew (Box 2638, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Luther (Box 2638, Folder 12)
  - Davis, Maclin Paschall and Edith Davis (Wife) (Box 2638, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Minnie E. (Box 2638, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Norman Hezekiah (Box 2638, Folder 15)
  - Davis, Percy Moore (Box 2638, Folder 16)
  - Davis, Rascoe Bond (Box 2638, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Ripley St. John (Box 2638, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Robert Lee (Box 2638, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Robert Morrison (Box 2638, Folder 20)
  - Davis, Robert William and Grace Flippin (Wife) (Box 2638, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Robert Windell (Box 2638, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Roger C. (Box 2638, Folder 23)
  - Davis, Samuel C. (Box 2638, Folder 24)
  - Davis, Samuel Y. (Box 2638, Folder 25)
  - Davis, Shelah Dillard (Box 2638, Folder 26)
  - Davis, Thomas (Box 2638, Folder 27)
  - Davis, Thomas Jackson (Box 2638, Folder 28)
  - Davis, Thomas Walker (Box 2638, Folder 29)
  - Davis, Thurman Jefferson (Box 2638, Folder 30)
  - Davis, Walter Naylor, Missouri Lieutenant Governor (Box 2638, Folder 31)
  - Davis, Walter Thomas (Box 2638, Folder 32)
  - Davis, William Anthony (Box 2638, Folder 33)
  - Davis, William Harold (Box 2638, Folder 34)
  - Davis, William Louis (Box 2638, Folder 35)
  - Davis, William Robert (Box 2638, Folder 36)
  - Davison, Augustus (Box 2638, Folder 37)
  - Davison, Charles L. (Box 2638, Folder 38)
  - Davitt, Charles (Box 2638, Folder 39)
  - Dawkins, Inez Shipp Gregory (Mrs. Thomas C. Dawkins) (Box 2638, Folder 40)
  - Dawson, James Robertson (Box 2638, Folder 41)
  - Day, Frank Leighton (Box 2638, Folder 42)
  - Day, Frank Pattison (Box 2638, Folder 43)
  - Day, Laurel J. (Box 2638, Folder 44)
  - Day, Nathaniel (Box 2638, Folder 45)
  - Dazey, William Lea (Box 2638, Folder 46)
  - Day, William Newton (Box 2638, Folder 47)
  - Dayton, Donald G. (Box 2638, Folder 48)
  - Dayton, Eva Shappard (Box 2638, Folder 49)
  - Deacon, Warren McAllister (Box 2638, Folder 50)
  - Deaderick, William Heiskell (Box 2638, Folder 51)
  - Deal, John (Box 2638, Folder 52)
  - Dealy, Robert J. (Box 2638, Folder 53)
  - Dean, Alvin Henry (Box 2638, Folder 54)
  - Dean, Charles Hermon (Box 2638, Folder 55)
  - Dean, John Randolph (Box 2638, Folder 56)
  - Dean, William Frank, Photo (Box 2638, Folder 57)
  - Dearing, William B. (Box 2638, Folder 58)
  - Dearman, James Robert (Box 2638, Folder 59)
  - Deatherage, Samuel Gall (Box 2638, Folder 60)
  - Deats, Charles W. (Box 2638, Folder 61)
  - Debardeleben, John T. (Box 2638, Folder 62)
  - DeBow, James Dunwoody Brownson (Box 2638, Folder 63)
  - DeBow, John Marshall (Box 2638, Folder 64)
  - Dechicclis, Ellen (Box 2638, Folder 65)
  - Dechman, Daniel Woodworth (Box 2638, Folder 66)
  - DeCourcy, Neil Cornelius (Box 2638, Folder 67)
  - Dedman, Bertram Cottingham (Box 2638, Folder 68)
  - Dedman, Robert C. (Box 2638, Folder 69)
  - Dedman, William Morgan (Box 2638, Folder 70)
  - Deeds, Edward Allen (Box 2638, Folder 71)
  - Deegan, Dorothy Jane Burke (Mrs. Lewis J. Deegan) (Box 2638, Folder 72)
  - Deer, George Anthony and Christine Perry (Wife) (Box 2638, Folder 73)
  - Deering, Ashby (Box 2638, Folder 74)
  - Deering, Robert Waller (Box 2638, Folder 75)
  - DeFord, James Pitts (Box 2638, Folder 76)
  - DeJarnatt, B. M. (Box 2638, Folder 77)
  - Delafield, William Pleasant (Box 2638, Folder 78)
  - DeLay, William Dewey (Box 2638, Folder 79)
  - Delbruck, Max, Nobel Prize Winner (Box 2638, Folder 80)
  - Delcher, Harry Ray (Box 2638, Folder 81)
  - Demaree, Thomas Walter Bascom (Box 2638, Folder 82)
  - Demos, Raphael (Box 2638, Folder 83)
  - Dempsey, Elam Franklin (Box 2638, Folder 84)
  - Dempsey, Robert Chaffee (Box 2638, Folder 85)
  - Denning, Armistead Otey (Box 2638, Folder 86)
  - Denning, Henry Duval (Box 2638, Folder 87)
  - Dennis, Edward Colgate (Box 2638, Folder 88)
  - Dennis, Roy Jones (Box 2638, Folder 89)
  - Dennis, Royal Franklin (Box 2638, Folder 90)
  - Dennison, Doris Pearl (Box 2638, Folder 91)
  - Dennison, Joseph Owen (Box 2638, Folder 92)
  - Dent, Clarence Turner (Box 2638, Folder 93)
  - Dent, Henry A. (Box 2638, Folder 94)
  - Dent, Wilbur Thomas (Box 2638, Folder 95)
  - Dent, Wilbur Tillett and Katherine Provost Kennedy (1st Wife) and Marguerite Dozier Gordon (2nd Wife) (Box 2638, Folder 96)
  - Dentici, Joseph Anthony (Box 2638, Folder 97)
  - Denton, Boone (Box 2638, Folder 98)
  - Denton, Edward Kendrick (Box 2638, Folder 99)
  - Denton, Guy Tressley (Box 2638, Folder 100)
  - Denton, Samuel (Box 2638, Folder 101)
  - DePierri, Bernard Leon (Box 2638, Folder 102)
  - DePierri, Bernard Watts (Box 2638, Folder 103)
  - DePoister, W. Marshon (Box 2638, Folder 104)
  - DePriest, John Lucian (Box 2638, Folder 105)
  - Derivaux, Robert C. (Box 2638, Folder 106)
  - Derring, Paul Neyron (Box 2638, Folder 107)
  - Desch, Sarah Hughes Logue (Box 2638, Folder 108)
  - Desissard, Marie (George H. Dudley, Junior - Husband) (Box 2638, Folder 109)
  - Detty, Victor Charles (Box 2638, Folder 110)
  - Deutschberger, Paul A. (Box 2638, Folder 111)
  - Deveneau, Louise Ingram Adamson (Mrs. Willard Francis Deveneau) (Box 2638, Folder 112)
  - Devito, Michael Joseph (Box 2638, Folder 113)
  - Devoe, John Mixsell, Photo (Box 2638, Folder 114)
  - DeWitt, John Hibbett, Photo (Box 2638, Folder 115)
  - DeWitt, Paul M. (Box 2638, Folder 116)
  - DeWitt, Ward (Box 2638, Folder 117)
  - Dews, Mary Cecil Morrison (Mrs. Richard P. Dews) (Box 2638, Folder 118)
  - Dexter, Eugene Hamilton (Box 2638, Folder 119)
  - Dial, John Degraffenreid, Photo (Box 2638, Folder 120)
  - Dial, Nathanial B., Photo; United States Senator (South Carolina) (Box 2638, Folder 121)
  - Dial, Virgil Andrew (Box 2638, Folder 122)
  - Diaz de Leon, Jose T. (Box 2638, Folder 123)
  - Dickens, Robert D. (Box 2638, Folder 124)
  - Dickenson, Robert Edward (Box 2638, Folder 125)
  - Dicky, Charles William (Box 2638, Folder 126)
  - Dickinson, Charles Kimbrough (Box 2638, Folder 127)
  - Dickinson, Henry (Box 2638, Folder 128)
  - Dickinson, J. M. (Box 2638, Folder 129)
  - Dickinson, John Overton (Box 2638, Folder 130)
  - Dickinson, Thomas Page (Box 2638, Folder 131)
  - Dickinson, Walker Philip (Box 2638, Folder 132)
  - Dickson, Felix Grundy (Box 2638, Folder 133)
  - Dickson, John I. (Box 2638, Folder 134)
  - Didcoct, John William (Box 2638, Folder 135)
  - Dietrich, C. J. (Box 2638, Folder 136)
  - Diggs, Graham Wall (Box 2638, Folder 137)
  - Dillard, Charles Garrison (Box 2638, Folder 138)
  - Dillard, James H. (Box 2638, Folder 139)
  - Dillard, Jeff (Box 2638, Folder 140)
  - Dillin, Jefferson Davis (Box 2638, Folder 141)
  - Dillingham, Charles Kollock (Box 2638, Folder 142)
  - Dillon, Leo Boggan (Box 2638, Folder 143)
  - Dillon, William Wesley (Box 2638, Folder 144)
  - Dinkins, Paul (Box 2638, Folder 145)
  - Dinning, John Henry (Box 2638, Folder 146)
  - Dinning, William Groves (Box 2638, Folder 147)
  - Dinning, Woodford Wilson (Box 2638, Folder 148)
  - Dinsmore, William Lewis (Box 2638, Folder 149)
  - Disharoon, Hugh Beaurgard (Box 2638, Folder 150)
  - Dismukes, Albert Roberts (Box 2638, Folder 151)
  - Dismukes, James Taylor (Box 2638, Folder 152)
  - Dismukes, John Frederick (Box 2638, Folder 153)
  - Diveley, Walter Lowell (Box 2638, Folder 154)
  - Dix, Clarice Belle (Box 2638, Folder 155)
  - Dixon, Alexander Travis (Box 2638, Folder 156)
  - Dixon, Hugh (Box 2638, Folder 157)
  - Dixon, John L. (Box 2638, Folder 158)
  - Dixon, John Wesley and Margaret Collins Denny (Wife) (Box 2638, Folder 159)
  - Dixon, Kenneth (Box 2639, Folder 1)
  - Dixon, Minnie McClellan (Box 2639, Folder 2)
  - Dixon, Virginia Butler (Mrs. Francis S. Dixon) (Box 2639, Folder 3)
  - Dixon, Zeno Hadley (Box 2639, Folder 4)
  - Doak, Archibald A. (Box 2639, Folder 5)
  - Doak, E. Lockhart (Box 2639, Folder 6)
  - Doak, James Robert (Box 2639, Folder 7)
  - Doane, Nathan Caldwell (Box 2639, Folder 8)
  - Dobbs, Hoyt McWhorter, Photo (Box 2639, Folder 9)
  - Dobbs, Hoyt McWhorter (Junior) (Box 2639, Folder 10)
  - Dobson, A. S. Newton (Box 2639, Folder 12)
  - Dodd, James W., Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse Club Leader (Box 2639, Folder 13)
  - Dodd, Robert Fite (Box 2639, Folder 14)
  - Dodge, Albert Charles (Box 2639, Folder 15)
  - Dodgen, Charles L. (Box 2639, Folder 16)
  - Dodson, Bluford Warren (Box 2639, Folder 17)
  - Dodson, David Wesley (Box 2639, Folder 18)
  - Dodson, James Elias, First Graduating Class of Vanderbilt University 1875 (Box 2639, Folder 19)
  - Dodson, Joseph Egbert Enloe (Box 2639, Folder 20)
  - Dodson, Kavanaugh Watts (Box 2639, Folder 21)
  - Dodson, Mayhew Wilson (Box 2639, Folder 22)
  - Dodson, Mayhew Wilson Pat (Box 2639, Folder 23)
  - Dodson, Stephen D. (Box 2639, Folder 24)
  - Dodson, Stonewall J. (Box 2639, Folder 25)
  - Dodson, William Curd (Box 2639, Folder 26)
  - Dollar, Charlie Carl (Box 2639, Folder 27)
  - Dollar, Jesse Holliday and Fannie Mae Elder (Wife) (Box 2639, Folder 28)
  - Donald, Edwin Cox (Box 2639, Folder 29)
  - Donald, John Watson (Box 2639, Folder 30)
  - Donaldson, George Hiram (Box 2639, Folder 31)
  - Donaldson, Meriwether Rivers (Box 2639, Folder 32)
  - Donaldson, Paul (Box 2639, Folder 33)
  - Donelson, Andrew Jackson (Box 2639, Folder 34)
  - Donelson, John (Box 2639, Folder 35)
  - Donnald, Edgar Razor (Box 2639, Folder 36)
  - Donnell, Charles E. (Box 2639, Folder 37)
  - Donnell, Herbert (Box 2639, Folder 38)
  - Donnelly, Arthur DeVries (Box 2639, Folder 39)
  - Donoho, Albert Gallatin (Box 2639, Folder 40)
  - Donoho, Charles Kerr (Box 2639, Folder 41)
  - Donoho, Joseph (Box 2639, Folder 42)
  - Donoho, Larry More (Box 2639, Folder 43)
  - Donohoo, Philip (Box 2639, Folder 44)
  - Doolin, Milford Elliott (Box 2639, Folder 45)
  - Doran, Paul Emerson (Box 2639, Folder 46)
  - Dorgan, John H. (Box 2639, Folder 47)
  - Dorian, John Steele (Box 2639, Folder 48)
  - Dorman, Lewy (Box 2639, Folder 49)
  - Dornblaser, Harry E. (Box 2639, Folder 50)
  - Dorris, Andrew Currey (Box 2639, Folder 51)
  - Dorris, G. Preston (Box 2639, Folder 52)
  - Dorris, George Milton (Box 2639, Folder 53)
  - Dortch, Della (Box 2639, Folder 54)
  - Dortch, Frederick William (Box 2639, Folder 55)
  - Dortch, Josiah Higgason (Box 2639, Folder 56)
  - Dortch, Thomas Steele (Box 2639, Folder 57)
  - Doss, Leslie Walter, Photo (Box 2639, Folder 58)
  - Doss, Washington Lafayette (Box 2639, Folder 59)
  - Doss, William Lafayette (Box 2639, Folder 60)
  - Dosser, James Harry (Box 2639, Folder 61)
  - Dossett, William Dixon (Box 2639, Folder 62)
  - Doster, Howard S. (Box 2639, Folder 63)
  - Dotson, Louis E. (Box 2639, Folder 64)
  - Dotson, R. E. (Box 2639, Folder 65)
  - Doubleday, Mary Love (Box 2639, Folder 66)
  - Doud, Rosa Ambrose (Mrs. Ralph Bingham Doud) (Box 2639, Folder 67)
  - Douglas, Arthur Henry (Box 2639, Folder 68)
  - Douglas, Bruce (Box 2639, Folder 69)
  - Douglas, Byrd (Box 2639, Folder 70)
  - Douglas, Hamilton (Box 2639, Folder 71)
  - Douglas, Lee (Box 2639, Folder 72)
  - Douglas, Richard (Box 2639, Folder 73)
  - Douglas, Samuel (Box 2639, Folder 74)
  - Douglas, William E. (Box 2639, Folder 75)
  - Douglass, Roy A. and Ellenna Webb (Wife), Photo (Box 2639, Folder 76)
  - Dowd, Dorothy E. Donley (Mrs. Thomas P. Dowd) (Box 2639, Folder 77)
  - Dowdle, Taylor Aylette (Box 2639, Folder 78)
  - Dowdy, James Arthur (Box 2639, Folder 79)
  - Dowell, Willis Bolivar (Box 2639, Folder 80)
  - Dowling, Hardee B. (Box 2639, Folder 81)
  - Dowling, Noel Thomas (Box 2639, Folder 82)
  - Dowling, Oscar (Box 2639, Folder 83)
  - Downer, Benjamin Reno (Box 2639, Folder 84)
  - Downer, Mary E. Boddie (Box 2639, Folder 85)
  - Downey, Jesse S. (Box 2639, Folder 86)
  - Downing, Evelyn Vaughn Early (Box 2639, Folder 87)
  - Downing, John R. (Box 2639, Folder 88)
  - Downs, Lawrence Etha (Box 2639, Folder 89)
  - Downs, Pinckney Lovick (Box 2639, Folder 90)
  - Downs, William Gershom (Box 2639, Folder 91)
  - Downs, William Gershom (Junior) (Box 2639, Folder 92)
  - Doxtator, Arlene (Mrs. Jimerson) (Box 2639, Folder 93)
  - Doyle, John Adams (Box 2639, Folder 94)
  - Dozier, Douglas (Box 2639, Folder 95)
  - Dozier, Edwin Lee (Box 2639, Folder 96)
  - Dozier, Howard Douglas (Box 2639, Folder 97)
  - Dozier, Jesse Emmett (Box 2639, Folder 98)
  - Dozier, Robert Lee (Box 2639, Folder 99)
  - Drace, Claude G. (Box 2639, Folder 100)
  - Drain, Karl E. (Box 2639, Folder 101)
  - Drake, Albion Caswell (Box 2639, Folder 102)
  - Drake, B. F. (Box 2639, Folder 103)
  - Drake, Benjamin McGruder (Box 2639, Folder 104)
  - Drake, John Richard (Box 2639, Folder 105)
  - Drake, Nell (Box 2639, Folder 106)
  - Drake, Werter Lewis (Box 2639, Folder 107)
  - Drake, William Winans (Box 2639, Folder 108)
  - Drane, Myrtle (Box 2639, Folder 109)
  - Drane, William McClure (Box 2639, Folder 110)
  - Draper, Thomas Jefferson (Box 2639, Folder 111)
  - Draper, Walter Scott (Box 2639, Folder 112)
  - Draper, Walter Scott (III) (Box 2639, Folder 113)
  - Draughn, Duncan McInnis (Box 2639, Folder 114)
  - Draughon, Louis R. (Box 2639, Folder 115)
  - Drennan, John Craddock (Box 2639, Folder 116)
  - Dresslar, Oscar Welborn and Frances Allina Armistead (Wife) (Box 2639, Folder 117)
  - Dreyfus, Alex F. (Box 2639, Folder 118)
  - Drinkwater, John A. (Box 2639, Folder 119)
  - Driscoll, Daniel J. (Box 2639, Folder 120)
  - Drisdale, Joseph Nathan (Box 2639, Folder 121)
  - Driskill, Andrew Jackson (Box 2639, Folder 122)
  - Driver, Carl Samuel (Box 2639, Folder 123)
  - Driver, Seaborne Algernon (Box 2639, Folder 124)
  - Drouillard, J. Pierre (Box 2639, Folder 125)
  - DuBois, Charley Joseph (Box 2639, Folder 126)
  - DuBois, Henry Harris Slaton (Box 2639, Folder 127)
  - DuBois, Ivan Cordell (Box 2639, Folder 128)
  - DuBose, Amasa John (Box 2639, Folder 129)
  - DuBose, Henry Wade (Box 2639, Folder 130)
  - Duckett, John Davis (Box 2639, Folder 131)
  - Duckworth, Guilford Marvin (Box 2639, Folder 132)
  - Duckworth, William Capell (Box 2639, Folder 133)
  - Dudley, Anna Willis Dallas (Mrs. Guilford Dudley, Senior) (Box 2639, Folder 134)
  - Dudley, Bunyan S. (Box 2639, Folder 135)
  - Dudley, Byron Stathan (Box 2639, Folder 136)
  - Dudley, George Harold (Box 2639, Folder 137)
  - Dudley, Joseph H. (Box 2639, Folder 138)
  - Dudley, Nicholas Lee (Box 2639, Folder 139)
  - Dudley, Sidney Johnston (Box 2639, Folder 140)
  - Dudley, William Lofland (Box 2639, Folder 141)
  - Duff, Price Hope (Box 2639, Folder 142)
  - Dufilho, Leon George (Box 2639, Folder 143)
  - Duflot, Joesph Leo (Box 2639, Folder 144)
  - Duggan, Snethon Burroughs (Box 2639, Folder 145)
  - Dugger, James Ernest (Box 2639, Folder 146)
  - Duke, Charles Talbot (Box 2639, Folder 147)
  - Duke, John Borns (Box 2639, Folder 148)
  - Duke, Raphael S. (Box 2639, Folder 149)
  - Dula, Frederick Mast (Box 2639, Folder 150)
  - Dulaney, John Jefferson, Arkansas State Senator (Box 2639, Folder 151)
  - Duling, Albert (Box 2639, Folder 152)
  - Dumville, Samuel Lawrence (Box 2639, Folder 153)
  - Dunbar, Charles Gibbs (Box 2639, Folder 154)
  - Dunbar, Clement Evans (Box 2639, Folder 155)
  - Dunbar, James Stewart (Box 2639, Folder 156)
  - Duncan, Berry Jackson (Box 2639, Folder 157)
  - Duncan, Charles Benjamin (Box 2639, Folder 158)
  - Duncan, Charles Bernard (Box 2639, Folder 159)
  - Duncan, Charles Gilderay (Box 2639, Folder 160)
  - Duncan, Edgar Hill (Box 2639, Folder 161)
  - Duncan, Harry Buttorff (Box 2639, Folder 162)
  - Duncan, Holmes Longstreet (Box 2639, Folder 163)
  - Duncan, Joseph J. (Box 2639, Folder 164)
  - Duncan, Marvin Theophilus (Box 2639, Folder 165)
  - Duncan, Richard (Box 2639, Folder 166)
  - Duncan, William Adolphus (Box 2639, Folder 167)
  - Duncan, William Mason (Box 2639, Folder 168)
  - Dungan, James Forney (Box 2639, Folder 169)
  - Dungan, William Thompson (Box 2639, Folder 170)
  - Dunham, H. Warren (Box 2639, Folder 171)
  - Dunham, Howard Walter (Box 2639, Folder 172)
  - Dunkerly, James Herbert (Box 2639, Folder 173)
  - Dunkle, William Frederick (Box 2639, Folder 174)
  - Dunklin, Frank B. (Box 2639, Folder 175)
  - Dunlap, Arthur C. (Box 2639, Folder 176)
  - Dunlap, Miles D. (Box 2639, Folder 177)
  - Dunlap, Perry G. (Box 2639, Folder 178)
  - Dunlop, William Barrett (Box 2639, Folder 179)
  - Dunn, Charles L. (Box 2639, Folder 180)
  - Dunn, G. A. (Box 2639, Folder 181)
  - Dunn, Henry Smith (Box 2639, Folder 182)
  - Dunn, James Edwin (Box 2639, Folder 183)
  - Dunn, James Washington (Box 2639, Folder 184)
  - Dunn, Lawrence T. (Box 2639, Folder 185)
  - Dunn, Merle Arna (Box 2639, Folder 186)